Howard Wise Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1943-1967, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-2; 2.0 linear ft.)
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1943-1967, 1.1:
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1956-1964 (Box 2)
      Morris International Gallery Limited, Jerrold
      Morris, Robert and Eleanor
      Morris, Mrs. William
      Morse, A. Reynolds
      Morton, Alastair
      Moss, Moe
      Motion Picture Association of America, Inc.
      Motive Magazine
      Mount Sinai Hospital of Cleveland
      Mount Union College
      Multiplex Display Fixture Co.
      Mundane Club
      Munro, Eleanor
      Murphy, Gerald
      Murray Co., George A.
      Musée National d'Art Moderne
      Museum of Fine Arts, Houston
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1959-1963, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Myers, Forrest - Palmer, A., 1952-1963 (Box 2)
      Myers, Forrest
      Nasher, Raymond D.
      Nassau, Jason
      National Conference of Christians and Jews
      National Council of Jewish Women, Inc., North Essex Section (see: Charity Exhibitions)
      National Institute of Arts and Letters
      National Jewish Monthly
      Nelson Gallery of Art, William R.
      Neuberger, Roy
      Neuman, Eckhard
      Nevelson, Mike
      Newark Museum
      New Canaan Library Art Committee
      Newhouse, Mrs. Samuel I.
      Newman, Muriel
      Newsweek
      New York Graphic Society
      New York Herald Tribune
      New York Public Library
      New Yorker
      Night in Budapest Committee
      Nolan, Mildred
      Nordness Gallery
      Noyes, Eliot
      N. W. Ayer and Son, Inc. (see: Ayer and Son, Inc., N. W.)
      Oakwood Club
      Obata, Gyo
      Obelisco Gallery, L'
      Obelisk Gallery
      Ohio Desk Company
      Ohio Society of New York
      Ohio University
      Oliphant, Stephen D.
      Olivier, Lawrence
      Orleans Gallery
      Orswell, Lois
      Otto Gerson Gallery, Inc. (see: Gerson Gallery, Otto)
      Overton, Douglas
      Oxford University Press
      Pahlmann, William
      Palmer, A.
    - Panza, Giuseppe - Pyrotronics, 1958-1967 (Box 2)
      Panza, Giuseppe
      Park Crescent Hotel
      Parks, Anita Jackson
      Parsons, Betty
      Payson, Hal
      Penney, Charles
      Pennsylvania State University
      Peratt, Valentine
      Peterson, Thomas F.
      Phipps, T. J.
      Piccarello, Frank, Jr.
      Pictures on Exhibit
      Pirandello
      Polaroid Corporation
      Pollock, Lewis G.
      Pollock, Peter
      Pond, Pearl Cowles
      Poole College
      Poole, Lynn
      Portable Gallery Color Slides
      Posner, Henry, Sr.
      Print Club of Cleveland
      Print Council of America
      Pryun, Mrs. R. L.
      Purdue University
      Putnam, John B.
      PVI Gallery
      Pyrotronics
    - Rapuano, Michael - Rutgers University, 1952-1964 (Box 2)
      Rapuano, Michael
      Ratner, Anne
      Rattner, Abraham
      Redfern Gallery, Ltd.
      Reichel, Miriam Brudno
      Reichold, Henry H.
      Relph, Grace
      Revel Travel Service
      Reynolds, R. S., Jr.
      Richards, Meryl
      Richelle Gallery
      Rillison, Mrs. Lawrence
      Rindler, L. A.
      Ringling Museum of Art, John and Mabel
      Roanoke Fine Arts Center
      Robertson, Bryan
      Robles Gallery, Esther
      Robson, Elizabeth Stone
      Rockefeller
      Rockefeller, David
      Rockefeller Institute
      Rockefeller, Nelson A.
      Rodriguez, Marcial
      Roland deAenllie Gallery (see: deAenllie Gallery, Roland)
      Rome-New York Art Foundation, Inc.
      Rose Fried Gallery (see: Fried Gallery, Rose)
      Rosen, Israel
      Rosenberg, Mrs. Edwin
      Rosenthal, Arthur J.
      Rothstsein, Anna
      Rowfant Club
      R. Scherer, Inc. (see: Scherer Inc., R.)
      Rubin, William S.
      Rubinfield, Donald
      Russell, Alfred
      Rutgers University
    - Sachs Gallery, A. M. - Segy Gallery, 1949-1966 (Box 2)
      Sachs Gallery, A. M.
      Saidenberg, Eleanor
      Saint Mary's College
      St. Moritz Hotel
      Salant, Mrs. Walter
      Salon de Mai
      Salt Lake City Public Library
      Saltonstall, Nathaniel
      Sampliner, Mrs. Paul
      Sanborn, William E.
      Sandbert, W.
      Santa Barbara Museum of Art
      Sarnoff, Robert
      Saturday Review
      Scaife, Richard M.
      Schaefer Gallery, Bertha
      Scherer Inc., R.
      Schermerhorn Gallery
      Schloss, Charles M.
      Schmalenbach, Werner
      Schmeller, Alfred
      Schmitt, Dorothy
      Schofield, Barbara
      School Art League
      Schreiber, Taft B.
      Schultz, Olga
      Schultz Roofing, P. W.
      Schwartz, Charles
      Scientific American
      Seattle Post Intelligencer
      Segal, Walter
      Seglen, Philip M.
      Segrestan, Mrs. Jacque
      Segy Gallery
    - Seiberling, J. Fred - Speyer, Darthea, 1957-1964 (Box 2)
      Seiberling, J. Fred
      Selby, Lynn
      Selden, George
      Seuphon, Michel
      Seymour, William and Florence
      Shaker Heights City School District
      Shaker Square Travel Service
      Sheldon, Albert M.
      Shestack, M. M.
      Short Run Color Corporation
      Show Magazine
      Sidney Janis Gallery (see: Janis Gallery, Sidney)
      Siff, Aida d'Agostino
      Singer, Mrs. Albert
      Singer Company
      Skidmore College
      Skidmore, Owings and Merrill
      Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture
      Sloan Gallery of American Painting
      Sloss, Lily
      Smith, C. Lee, Jr.
      Smith, D. C.
      Smith, Frank F.
      Smith, Ray
      Smoluchowski, Roman
      Society for the Advancement of Judaism
      Society of Gourmets for the Leisure Arts, Inc.
      Solinger, David M. and Hope
      Soltz, Al
      Southern Illinois University
      Special Surveys
      Sperling, Mrs. Milton
      Sperry, Victoria
      Speyer, Darthea
    - Spock, Benjamin - Syracuse University, 1957-1964 (Box 2)
      Spock, Benjamin
      Springger-Penquin Company
      Sprinzen, Harold
      Stable Gallery
      Staempfeli Gallery, Inc.
      Stamford Jewish Center
      State Teachers College (Slippery Rock, Pa.)
      State University College (Fredonia, N. Y.)
      State University of Iowa
      Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences
      Stedelijk van Abbemuseum Eindhoven
      Stein, Ronald
      Steinberg, Saul
      Stewart, Sam E.
      Stillman, Rufus C.
      Stockton, Robert S. and Ann
      Stone Gallery, Alan
      Stone, David C.
      Stowe Area Association, Inc.
      Strauss, Marion
      Streitmann, A. P.
      Stroup, Beatrice Moore
      Strub, Henry
      Studio Magazine
      Suburban Temple Women's Committee
      Swarthmore College
      Sweeney, James Johnson
      Sylvester, Edmund
      Syracuse University
    - Tanager Gallery - United States Steel Corporation, 1950-1966 (Box 2)
      Tanager Gallery
      Tangerman, R. S.
      Tannhauser, Justin
      Tate Gallery
      Tatelbaum, Harriet
      Taylor, Jay
      Taylor, Elizabeth
      Taylor, William and Jean
      Techbuilt, Inc.
      Temple
      Temple B'nai Sholom (see: Charity Exhibitions)
      Temple Emanuel
      Ten Thirty Gallery
      Tenenbaum, Frieda
      Thibaut Gallery
      Tiffany and Co.
      Tile Classics
      Tishman, Robert V.
      Titelman, Mrs. Frank M.
      Toledo Museum of Art
      Tooth and Sons, Ltd., Arthur
      Tower Fellowship
      Tower Press
      Tremco Manufacturing Company
      Trenton State College
      Trigg, Ernest T.
      True Magazine
      Tudor, Charles
      Tudor Publishing Co.
      Turn Toward Peace (see: Charity Exhibitions)
      Tuttie, Irwin and Nancy
      Twentieth Century Gallery
      Tyson Operating Company, Inc.
      Ullman, A. James
      UNICEF
      Uniontown Friends of Art Committee
      United Air Lines
      United Appeal of Greater Cleveland
      United Jewish Appeal of Greater New York
      United Palestine Appeal
      United States Customs
      United States Department of Commerce
      United States Information Agency
      United States Post Office
      United States Steel Corporation
    - University of Alabama - Waldorf, Dorothy Densmore, 1957-1964 (Box 2)
      University of Alabama
      University of Illinois
      University of Massachusetts
      University of Michigan
      University of Minnesota
      University of Pennsylvania
      University of Pittsburgh
      University of St. Thomas
      University of Southern Illinois
      University of Washington
      University School Alumni Association
      Vaiksnoras, Anthony J.
      Van der Beek, Stan
      Van der Marck, Jan H.
      Van Dyke, J. Brooks
      Vanik, Charles A.
      Venice Bienale
      Verlag M. Dumont Schauberg
      Village Voice
      Viviano, Catherine
      Vocational Guidance and Rehabilitation Services
      Vogel, Amos
      Waddington Galleries
      Wade, Jeptha H.
      Wake Forest College
      Walden School
      Waldhorns Interiors
      Waldorf, Dorothy Densmore
    - Walker Art Center, 1958-1964, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Walkup, Park E. - Western Adjustment and Inspection Co., 1951-1964 (Box 2)
      Walkup, Park E.
      Wallace, Sylvia C.
      Walling, Hayden
      Walter Landor and Associates (see: Landor and Associates, Walter)
      Ware, Paul and Betty
      Warwick and Legler, Inc. Advertising
      Wayne, June
      WDOK Radio
      Wise, Samuel D.
      Webb Chapter No. 14, Royal Arch Masons
      Weber, John
      Weese, Harry
      Weidler, Charlotte
      Weidlinger, Madeleine
      Weil, Freddie and Ann
      Weil, Eilene
      Weil, Helen L.
      Weil, R. K.
      Weil, Walter
      Weill, Guy and Lucy
      Weis, David and Jeanette
      Weisman, Fred
      Wellesley College
      Welton, Karlyn
      Wengroth, Richard A.
      Wenstrup, Margaret
      WERE Radio
      West Village Committee
      Westbury Hotel
      Western Adjustment and Inspection Co.
    - Western Reserve University (Box 2)
      - Advisory Committee on Music (re: affiliation with Cleveland Institute of Music), 1952-1953 (Box 2)
      - Correspondence with President John S. Millis and Others (Howard Wise, Trustee), 1951-1963 (Box 2)
      - "Looking at Modern Art" (study/discussion course held at Howard Wise Gallery), 1958-1959 (Box 2)
      - Visiting Committee on Visual Arts, 1957-1959 (Box 2)
    - Westlake Plastics Co. - Wofford College, 1957-1966 (Box 2)
      Westlake Plastics Co.
      Weston, S. Burns
      Westport Community Art Association
      Weyhe Gallery
      White, John F.
      Whitney Museum of American Art
      Wick, Kenneth B.
      Wickham, Ben
      Widdifield Gallery, Martin
      Wildenstein Gallery
      Wilder, Nicholas
      Wildwood, Camp
      Wilkinson, Kirk
      Willard Gallery
      William R. Nelson Gallery of Art (see: Nelson Gallery of Art, William R.)
      Williams, Kay
      Williams, Oscar
      Wilson, Ralph
      Winton, D. Mike
      Wise, John
      Wise, Victor
      Wittenberg Public Relations, Ernest
      Wixom, Nancy
      Woehle, Fritz
      Wofford College
    - Women's City Club of Cleveland, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
    - Wood, Remsen - Zimmerman, Mrs. Isadore J., 1957-1966 (Box 2)
      Wood, Remsen
      Woodward Foundation
      Woody, Russell O., Jr.
      Woollen, Evans
      Worcester Art Museum
      Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology
      World House Galleries
      WPAT Radio
      Wragge, Sydney
      Wurtzburger, Alan
      Wurzburger, Paul D.
      York, Scott R.
      Yoseido Gallery
      Young, Stephen M.
      Zabriskie Gallery
      Zadok, Charles
      Zanini, Walter
      Zegman, Freda
      Zero-Max Industries, Incorporated
      Zimmerman, Mrs. Isadore J.
  - New York Gallery Correspondence, 1962-1965, 1.2:
    This subseries consists of the correspondence of Howard Wise, several gallery employees, and art consultant Douglas MacAgy, and documents the operations and activities of Howard Wise Gallery, New York.
    - New York Gallery Correspondence, 1962-1965, (3 folders) (Box 3)
- Artist Files, 1950-1968, Series 2:; (Boxes 3-6; 3.25 linear ft.)
  Most artists represented in this series were affiliated with Howard Wise Gallery either in Cleveland or New York City, but some files are for individuals of possible interest to the gallery. Files contain varying combinations of correspondence, printed material, notes, writings, and photographs.
  Files are arranged alphabetically by artist name.
  - Aach, Herbert, 1960-1967, undated (Box 3)
  - Abend, George, 1950-1964, undated (Box 3)
  - Afro (Basaldella), 1957, undated (Box 3)
  - Ahr, Dick, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Akayavash (see: Erol) (Box 3)
  - Altamura, Frank P., 1960 (Box 3)
  - Aldcroft, Richard, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Altman, Harold, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
  - Armitage, Kenneth, undated (Box 3)
  - Barker, Walter, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Barnet, Will, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Barr, Norman, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Barré, Martin and Martine, 1957-1960 (Box 3)
  - Barry, Carver S., 1958 (Box 3)
  - Bayer, Herbert, 1957-1965, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Basaldella (see: Afro) (Box 3)
  - Bayliss, George, undated (Box 3)
  - Bell, Trevor, 1962, undated (Box 3)
  - Benton, Fletcher, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Bergman, Anna Eva, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Bergschneider, John, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Bernstein, Sylvia, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Berrocal, Miguel, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Bertrand, Huguette-Arthur, 1957-1963, undated (Box 3)
  - Bertschmann, Harry, 1957-1961 (Box 3)
  - Bhandt, Cort Leigh, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Birch, James A., 1959 (Box 3)
  - Bird, G., 1958 (Box 3)
  - Blake, John, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Blielfield, Stanley, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Blow, Sandra, 1958, undated (Box 3)
  - Bolomey, R. H., 1961 (Box 3)
  - Bookatz, Samuel, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Booth, Cameron, 1961-1965 (Box 3)
  - Brainard, Owen, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Braque, Georges, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Brenson, Theodore, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Briggs, Ernest, 1954-1964, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Brose, Morris, undated (Box 3)
  - Brown, Milton, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Buggiani, Paolo, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Burlin, Paul, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Cajori, Charles, 1961-1965, undated (Box 3)
  - Calcagno, Lawrence, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - Campitelli, Russell, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Casarella, Edmond, 1957-1961 (Box 3)
  - Cash, James G., undated (Box 3)
  - Celentano, Francis, 1964-1967, undated (Box 3)
  - Chagall, Marc, 1957-1960, undated (Box 3)
  - Chesini, Sergio Dino, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Christoforou, 1960-1961, undated (Box 3)
  - Citron, Mina, 1956-1959 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Ed, undated (Box 3)
  - Cook, Sally, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Corneille, 1953-1961, undated (Box 3)
  - Cox, J. Halley, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Cramer, Belle, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Crawford, Ralston, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Crehan, Hubert, undated (Box 3)
  - Davidson, Morris, 1959-1961 (Box 3)
  - Davis, Gene, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Day, Worden, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
  - de Botto, Jean, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
  - de Kooning, Elaine, 1959-1961, undated (Box 3)
  - de Martelli, John, undated (Box 3)
  - De Soto, Ernest, 1957-1961 (Box 3)
  - Dininno, Frank A., 1961 (Box 3)
  - Domato, Hisao, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Dominat, Paul, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Donahue, George, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Drew, Joan, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Drew, Ray, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Dugmore, Edward, 1954-1963, undated (Box 3)
  - Dumitresco, Natalia, 1958-1962, undated (Box 3)
  - Eckhardt, Edris, 1958-1961, undated (Box 3)
  - Edwards, Ethel, 1957-1961, undated (Box 3)
  - Elliott, Stanley B., 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Erlanger, Elizabeth N., 1959 (Box 3)
  - Erol (Akayavash), 1960 (Box 3)
  - Feeley, Paul, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Ferber, Herbert, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Ferren, John, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
  - Fieto, Luis, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Fine, Perle, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
  - Fogel, Seymour, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Fontana, Lucio, 1964-1966 (Box 3)
  - Forndran, Werner, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Fraenkel, Richard, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Francken, Ruth, 1956-1962, undated (Box 3)
  - Frank, Emily, 1962 (Box 3)
  - Frasconi, Antonio, undated (Box 3)
  - Freimark, Robert M., 1958 (Box 3)
  - Frost, Terry, 1958-1962, undated (Box 3)
  - Gardner, Joan Andrews, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Garelli, Franco, 1958-1960 (Box 3)
  - Gaudneck, Walter, 1960-1965,undated (Box 3)
  - Gauguin, Tom, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Geist, Stanley, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Gemberling, Kathleen, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Getman, William, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
  - Gilleran, Peter J., 1958 (Box 3)
  - Gillet, Roger Edgar, 1957-1962, undated (Box 3)
  - Gitelman, Belle S., 1961 (Box 3)
  - Gladstone, Gerald, 1960, undated (Box 3)
  - Glaser, Louis, 1961 (Box 3)
  - Goldberg, Dorothy, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Goldin, Leon, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Goldstein, Howard, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Gonzalez, Xavier, 1953-1965, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Goodspeed, Albert, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Goodyear, John, 1961-1968, undated (Box 4)
  - Grillo, John, 1955-1964, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Haacke, Hans, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - Haass, Terry, 1957-1958 (Box 4)
  - Haese, Gunter, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Hague, Raoul, 1959-1960 (Box 4)
  - Hammersley, Frederick, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Hartung, Hans, 1957-1961, undated (Box 4)
  - Hartung, Hans and Adja Yunkers, 1958, undated, (limited edition prints) (Box 4)
  - Hazelet, Sally, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Hepworth, Barbara, undated (Box 4)
  - Heron, Patrick, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Hess, Minda, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Hilton, Roger, 1959-1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Hios, Theo, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Horiuchi, Paul, undated (Box 4)
  - Horvath, Joseph, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
  - Hostetler, David, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Howard, Charles, 1956-1965 (Box 4)
  - Hulich, Josef, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Istrati, Alexandre, 1957-1965, undated (Box 4)
  - Jacobsen, Robert, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Jaeisch, Hans, 1956-1961 (Box 4)
  - Johnson, James, 1958-1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Jones, John Paul, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Kadish, Rueben, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Kaish, Morton, undated (Box 4)
  - Kane, Robert, 1958-1960 (Box 4)
  - Karoly, Fredric, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Kaufman, Irving, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1958-1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Kepes, Juliet, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
  - Kessanlis, Nikos (see: Nikos) (Box 4)
  - Koenig, John F., 1958-1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Kohn, Edmond, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Krasner, Lee, 1955-1964, undated, (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Krushenick, Nicholas, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Lamantina, James R., Jr., undated (Box 4)
  - Lamouroux, Jean, undated (Box 4)
  - Legare, Juliette, 1957-1958 (Box 4)
  - Leighton, Clare, 1957-1961, undated (Box 4)
  - Lekakis, Michael, 1959-1965, undated (Box 4)
  - Levee, John, 1957-1960, undated (Box 4)
  - Levi, Josef, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
  - Libal, Edward, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1955 (Box 4)
  - Lister, Jeanne, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Little, John, undated (Box 4)
  - Long, Hubert, 1960 (Box 4)
  - MacGibney, Bruce R., undated (Box 4)
  - Maddox, Jerrold, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Maisterra, N. Jose, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Malicoat, Philip C. 1959 (Box 4)
  - Malina, Frank, 1965-1967, undated (Box 4)
  - Manessier, Alfred, undated (Box 4)
  - Marsciano, Nicholas, 1962-1966, undated (Box 4)
  - Martine, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Mason, Alden C., 1961 (Box 4)
  - Masurovsky, Gregory, 1958-1963, undated (Box 4)
  - Matsumoto, Hozan, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Matta, Roberto, 1958 (Box 4)
  - Matthews, Joan, 1960 (Box 4)
  - Mattox, Charles, 1965-1967, undated (Box 4)
  - Mayhew, Richard C., undated (Box 4)
  - McGee, Winston, 1958-1961 (Box 4)
  - McManaway, David, 1966 (Box 4)
  - McVey, William, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Mefferd, Boyd, 1966-1968 (Box 4)
  - Meneeley, Edward, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Meo, Salvatore S., 1959 (Box 4)
  - Metzger, Hal, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Michaels, Glen, 1962 (Box 5)
  - Miguel, Cécile, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Millionzi, Victor, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Miró, Joan, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Madison Fred, 1957-1965, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Montgomery, Frank, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Morelett, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Morris, Kyle, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
  - Morris, William, 1962 (Box 5)
  - Morrison, Ruth, 1961-1964 (Box 5)
  - Morrow, Robert, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Morse, Breton, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Mosca, Ivan, 1957-1960, undated (Box 5)
  - Moy, Seong, 1957-1957 (Box 5)
  - Mueller, Robert, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Mullen, Albert, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Naberezny, Joh, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Nakian, Reuben, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Napoli, Giuseppi, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Nay, E. W., undated (Box 5)
  - Nelson, Rolf, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Nesbitt, Lowell, 1965-1968, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Nikos (Kessanlis), 1958-1962, undated (Box 5)
  - Noguchi, Isamu, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Oliver, F. M., 1967 (Box 5)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Ortman, George, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Ott, Lynfield, undated (Box 5)
  - Otta, Francesco, undated (Box 5)
  - Pace, Stephen, 1954-1964, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Pack, Rose H., 1960 (Box 5)
  - Paris, Harold, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Pavia, Philip, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Perilli, Achille, 1957-1960 (Box 5)
  - Phillips, Blanche, 1959, undated (Box 5)
  - Potter, Bernice, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Powell, John M., Jr., 1960 (Box 5)
  - Prokopoff, Stephen, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Rabkin Leo (Lights in Orbit show), 1967 (Box 5)
  - Raisen, Nathan, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Reed, Phyllis (see: Stewart, Macdonald) (Box 5)
  - Reeves, Paul, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Reinhardt, Ad, 1959-1963, undated (Box 5)
  - Renouf, Edward, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
  - Rickey, George, 1963-1967 (Box 5)
  - Riley, Bridget, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Rocklin, Raymond, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Rothko, Mark, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Salk, Rita Anne, undated (Box 5)
  - Salvatore, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
  - Samuels, Edward G. (Lights in Orbit Show), 1968 (Box 5)
  - Satok, Ronald, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Schanker, Louis, undated (Box 5)
  - Schiwetz, Bertold ("Tex"), 1957-1962 (Box 5)
  - Schlemowitz, Abram, 1960-1965, undated (Box 5)
  - Schock, William, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Schreiber, Martin, 1962 (Box 5)
  - Schucker, Charles, 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Schultze, Bernard, 1958-1957, undated, (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Sibley, Charles, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Sirugo, Sal, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Smith, David, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Smith, Mitchell, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
  - Smith, William G., Jr., 1958 (Box 5)
  - Soto, Jesus Raphael, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Soulages, Pierre, 1957-1960, undated (Box 5)
  - Soviak, Harry, 1958-1960 (Box 5)
  - Stasik, Andrew, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Stewart, Macdonald (Phyllis Reed), 1960 (Box 5)
  - Streeter, Tal, 1961 (Box 5)
  - Sugaï, Kumi, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
  - Takaezu, Toshiko, 1958-1961 (Box 5)
  - Takal, Peter, 1958-1960 (Box 5)
  - Tanaka, Flavio Shiro, undated (Box 5)
  - Tania, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Terbois, Pierre, undated (Box 5)
  - Turcato, Giulio, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Turnbull, William, 1959-1960, undated (Box 5)
  - Tworkov, Jack, 1960 (Box 5)
  - Valentin, Marcelle, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Van Dyk, James, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Van Leyden, Ernst, undated (Box 5)
  - Vaughan, Keith, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
  - Vavrushka, Frank, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Vazquez, Frank, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Vedova, Emilio, 1958-1961, undated (Box 5)
  - Von Wicht, John, 1957, undated (Box 5)
  - Wadowski, Alice T., 1957 (Box 6)
  - Walker, Clay, 1957-1961 (Box 6)
  - Warshaw, Laurence (Lights in Orbit show), 1967-1968, undated (Box 6)
  - Wayne, June, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Weatherspoon, Alexander, undated (Box 6)
  - Weber, Hugo, 1961-1968, undated (Box 6)
  - Weiner, Homer, 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Weinrib, David, 1960-1965, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Wheeler, Harry, 1959-1961 (Box 6)
  - Whiteside, Forbes, 1960-1961, undated (Box 6)
  - Whitman, Robert, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Wilke, Ulfert, 1953-1968, undated (Box 6)
  - Wilson, Frank Avary, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Winter, Fritz, 1955-1958, undated (Box 6)
  - Wynter, Bryan, 1959-1960 (Box 6)
  - Xceron, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Yamamoto, Taro, undated (Box 6)
  - Youngerman, R., 1957 (Box 6)
  - Yunkers, Adja (see: Hartung, Hans and Adja Yunkers) (Box 6)
  - Zaloudek, Duane, 1960 (Box 6)
- Exhibition Files, 1957-1968, Series 3:; (Boxes 6-7; 0.75 linear ft.)